OWASP Top 10 recap reinforces that application security is part of a broader ISO 27001
risk management and governance mindset.
Relationship between application security and ISO 27001 reinforces that application
security is part of a broader ISO 27001 risk management and governance mindset.
Risk management mindset reinforces that application security is part of a broader ISO
27001 risk management and governance mindset.
Use this course as an awareness and planning aid.
Validate control applicability with ISMS, audit, risk, and security stakeholders.
Maintain evidence for secure development, vulnerability management, access control,
monitoring, and remediation activities.
Selected ISO mappings for this topic include ISO/IEC 27001 - Information security
management system context;
ISO/IEC 27002 - Information security control guidance.